<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on UysDesign</title>
    <link>https://uysdesign.co.za/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on UysDesign</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 14:35:44 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://uysdesign.co.za/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://uysdesign.co.za/privacypolicy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 16:59:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uysdesign.co.za/privacypolicy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy We use your information to process your request for information, to deliver relevant information to you over time and to contact you about our services if they are relevant to you. We will never share any of your information with anyone else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://uysdesign.co.za/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 17:47:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uysdesign.co.za/about/</guid>
      <description>Who are we? We aren&#39;t just a marketing agency, we are digital artisans. We believe that the old-world skills of craftsmanship and precision that are only acquired with years of practice is still as important today as they were a thousand years ago.
Our mission UysDesign design was founded to help businesses achieve their full potentional and to survive and thrive in our trying economic environment. We realized very early in our journey that most businesses are not taking advantage of the incredible marketing tools that are available to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://uysdesign.co.za/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 17:14:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uysdesign.co.za/contact/</guid>
      <description> Contact Us info@uysdesign.co.za
(071)603-2866 If you want to book a meeting or if you just have a few questions, send us an email, or give us a call. Alternatively you can fill in the form below. Be sure the specify what you are contacting us about so we can help you more effectively.
Let&#39;s Talk Name Company Name(Optional) Email Query Send </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Services</title>
      <link>https://uysdesign.co.za/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 17:12:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uysdesign.co.za/services/</guid>
      <description>Our Services Below is a short summary of the services that we offer. We would encourage you to call us a soon as possible, because we strive to tailor our services to every client that we have and as such, we don&#39;t offer &#34;packages&#34;.
Contact Us Graphic Design A great way to make your business stand out instantly is a logo that pops and draws attention. To harness this more fully, we can create your whole branding package, from social media banners to business cards to flyers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
